And I zoomed in of your backdrop there. I love it.
Oh, thanks. Oh, uh, new addition, is it in here? Oh, yeah, right here.
I called Code or Anthropic reached out in an e-mail just telling me that I was a power user, and so I got like a card saying I'm a power user. I got some buttons, yeah, and then that little thing, and then a few other things.
BU.
I love that.
Is that like your official mascot?
Yeah, I guess so. Yeah.
Okay.
Like a little, ohh, cool.
Like if you open up like the desktop app, yeah, if you open up like the desktop app, that's kind of like what he looks like.
Okay, very cool.
Everybody getting in. Oh, let's invite Eric.
How's it going?
Great, how are you?
Dave up.
Good.
Look at the.
Oh, here it is, yeah.
See, they also sent me a hat because I'm also officially a power user. And then it said the little card just saying you're a power user and then like a little thing and then some stickers. So, hey, you know, you spend enough money on there, they give you a hat.
Wow.
Very cool.
I was gonna say you gotta you missed the plushy Eric. Check out my my kids would like the plushy.
And that was this.
Yeah.
What, uh, what app is that?
Anthropic, the cloud code, yeah.
Oh.
Okay.
I got an e-mail like, you're a power user. If you give us your address, we'll send you a gift. And I was like, why not? Whatever, like, do it. And yeah, and it just showed up with all the stills like, cool, why not? Like, yeah.
Why not?
Rice.
But we'll have to we'll have to create a power user gift pack, you know, for scribble for scribble families that you know go on they go 90 days without missing a scribble. I love it. So cool.
There you go.
Not bad yet.
All right, so I updated the meeting invite as well. I'll just go ahead and drop this in here now.
Yeah, slide to some person.
Will it not let me drop? External sharing is not allowed.
You know what's funny is when...
How am I an external?
It let me let Eric in, which was weird. It said, do you want to let him in?
I see that on Teams as well.
Yap.
I was like, I'm pretty sure I should have no permissions when it comes to teams. I have no clue what I'm doing.
Okay.
All right, if you guys would, in the meeting invite, there should be a scribble workshop HTML. If you guys could grab that.
So yeah, so this meeting is just going to be like our shape kickoff. Originally it was called like the, was it feature.
feature optimization or figuring out like the way in which to lay down features, but I mean, you guys lay down your cards and so I'll show you the backlog that we're starting to build out. But doing feature prioritization, I mean, right now kind of doesn't make sense. We'll have the backlog probably more in order, probably closer to like middle of, middle, beginning of next week.
because we just kind of laid down the epics and the features. So, and I will start sharing what this is on this diagram as well.
That link for me is just opening up a code dog.
I've got, I've got the dock.
It should be an HTML file, and as I said, I will I will share my screen and show that as well.
Me, it's just a large issue. I think I have the same thing.
Eric.
Yeah, I downloaded it and then once I downloaded it, like converted it for me. Yeah.
Okay, perfect. Yeah, so this is what it should show up as. And I just kind of put together a whole bunch of stuff just so you guys just have like an artifact of everything. So we have here's with the delivery team. One thing to note that I found out starting yesterday and today, our main iOS engineer that we had started with.
Okay, let me do that.
He has like a family emergency going on for this week and a little bit of next week. So unfortunately, he's unavailable right now. So we dropped him down to 30% and then they're bringing another iOS engineer on right now as we speak. And they should be like targeted, you know, tomorrow, today to start being brought on.
Yap.
I mean, as we're still building it out and getting devices to everybody, I mean, this is just to be expected; it just kind of happens, and then kind of, as you can see, I put scribble in here, and then we've kind of got just like the tentative dates for the windows for each of the sprints.
There is this open question set which we will go over. This open question set right here is actually backed by the Lucid board, which is also I put the link up on here as well. So if we click on here, this will take us right to the Lucid board. These are the open questions that
Yap.
The team, as myself, have for all of you, these are kind of like our, I'm going to make this kind of like our decision record. This way, then we can put our questions up here and then, you know, I can let you guys know, but then you can always come back in because you guys have access to this Lucid board and you can come in, fill in any information, fill in the decisions.
Back.
Where you say something?
No, no, I'm just following you. This is great.
Okay, yeah, yeah. I wanted to put it in a spot where like, I wasn't blocking the team, you weren't blocking me, you know, so everybody has access to this. So this way then anybody can come in here and add stuff, because even like me interacting with the team since they're in India, you know, there's only like a sliver of the morning that I really get with them. So like, I also needed a way in which to kind of like share stuff. So
We'll run through this in a moment because some of these are pretty big blockers and kind of like point like what we'll be doing in these first couple weeks. And really the iOS one is like the biggest blocker on here, but as I said, we'll get to that. So, all right, as I said, like that's what this kind of question set is and I kind of just wanted to give it to you.
I'm going to be scheduling a few more meetings today. So I'm going to schedule like our sprint demos for, and I don't know that we quite agreed on it, but I'll go ahead and put them Friday and then we can always, you know, readjust these. I'll get them out early enough to where we can, you know, fight over them in the, you know, in the ether of the future. Additionally,
I saw Christina's e-mail, Eric. So I was thinking if she wants to run through everything before she does any of the images and I need the designs kind of first. So I was thinking of maybe scheduling that meeting tomorrow for like an hour and I'll take like the current app and dump all the screens out for us.
Yap.
And do you want to do that in your Figma? Do you want to do that on my Lucid board? What's the best, like, because what you shared with me was on your Figma board. And if you just give me access to a board, I can drop the screenshots on here and then we can work from there if that works best for you all. You just let me know.
Yeah, you should have edit access to that, but I'll double check.
Possibly not, or you might be able to ping me for it.
I kind of, you know, I identified those three or four screens there that we would probably have her work out, being the intro screen, the home screen, and then whatever the shareable is for the single story, which might also carry over the artifact. I think if we were able to get those three or four screens from her, they're probably the key ones for me.
Mhm.
And then anything else can kind of trickle down from there using your methods.
Okay, okay, perfect, perfect, perfect. Because yeah, we'll get that meeting set up. And as I said, I'll try and get that set for tomorrow so we can start working on that as well.
So, as I said, I will schedule that.
And then yeah, and then we'll start getting you into the backlog, which is that I've also included that on here. As I said, this is like the initial backlog. I took all of the cards from our workshop. So you can actually, this is just a, you know, re-stylized version of the screenshots that we put on there, the stickies.
What?
So, it said here was like our green MVP list. We also then have our orange list down here, and then, as you can see, then the gray coming next. As you can see, I've already started to create epic numbers to kind of like, you know, when will those epic wise be, you know, future ready. And so, and then you know, more of your rules down here, and then if you start...
to get down into here now is where it's actually talking about the epics and then the features that we have laid out currently. I went ahead and I've also deployed A Sprint Zero. The Sprint Zero is more for the team. This is like for our QE lead.
You know, what is the testing framework you want to use? Why do you want to use it? You know, a lot of these things so that then, you know, we're also presenting in front of you, hey, this is why we chose this one. If you guys don't have an opinion on it, this is why we, you know, say you should use it. There's, you know, tasks for me for like creating the harness, things like that. And as I said, if you click on this, all of these are available so you can't see them.
These right here actually match to the actual Jira.
To our Jira, where I've actually I've put all of the current.
Epic Zero, so that's that first like Sprint Zero, as well as the first set of green is currently inside of our Jira board right now. Right now, this is in Jira, as I said, it's in a rough place. I believe we can actually just invite you guys so you can use it off to work with our IT to figure that out.
Sounds good.
Awesome. So let's go over some of the most important things. So I did update the POC. So this is the one that's in Vercel that is up. I took the initial screens that you gave me, Eric, the new wireframes.
And so I've kind of like readjusted the flow. I've tried to add the onboarding flow, the invite flow as much as I can, and add it. And right now, Claude is actually even working on the sharing feature, so we can actually see the share. So we might even get to see that, because that's actually what's running right here is this version is the actual share version running right now.
Right.
Yeah, so I want to walk through that now to kind of get some feedback so that then as I can tune this a little bit tonight, get all the screenshots up, and then be ready for tomorrow's one where then we can kind of really go through this and like flush out all these screens. But all right, I'll go ahead and do that. Which is, feel free, this is the exact same Vercel link.
and a password from before, which I will reshare that in the chat.
There you go. If you lost the link, that's the link in the password.
I am using the same Amazon AWS backend that we have right here. So you will see your original emails and everything still in here and then all of the individuals that you had added.
So as you can see right here on the sign up screen, I did add a new toggle because obviously we do want to keep creating new users to keep seeing this like brand new user onboarding. I just created a toggle for it, so it just makes it that much easier from the sign up screen. So we can toggle it on. And I'll do this for me. There you saw the little splash screen.
Now we come to the actual Scribble welcome. So we have our getting started. Now we go into here is now the Scribble prompt for the day, which I did take before I got your new set of prompts, the prompt package, which thank you, Eric, I'll start working on that. I did use the HTML or the packet that Matt had given me where it actually shared a whole bunch of information and like
what you even had in there, what bad prompts were and what good prompts were. So it actually built a pretty decent, just off of that, what you shared with me, Matt. So yeah, so we got to draw the sky outside right now.
Oh, so this one right here, I haven't quite updated it, but on this one, which will be future, you will have the new.
I did fix the colors that you just shared with me this morning, Eric. So yeah, so this will be fixed in the new one. And as I said, before tomorrow, I'll have that updated. So these are the colors that you suggested. So just why I did get that fixed. So as you can see right here, we have our draw what we see outside right now. So
Awesome.
Single cloud. Now on yours, you had this split screen. Before I had to where you could do the talking and it would do the speech to text translation. I got rid of that since you have either sharing your voice recording and hearing it or sharing your text. So we can actually do that two different ways. I'll do the recording one right now because this does work.
So now you come on here and is that I took your exact screen, so this should be modeled off of your screens, Eric.
Oh, I guess I'm not sharing it. So a single cloud outside a beautiful day.
And I think the thought with that screen in particular, while it might not carry through to the rest of the game, it was to very blatantly show people you could do one or the other and you needed to choose one. We have to be like super implicit with this onboarding because we've learned A lot. It's that people just don't get stuff. Yeah.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah, and so you can either playback, you can re-record, but now it actually saves that recording. And so then if I put this on my personal wall and I hit share, so okay, so now we got the rest of the onboarding experience. Now we're inside the application. So now if we come into here and we go to the personal wall,
So if I look at my most recent photo now, now you can see now there's the voice notes. Now if I actually hit play, I can hear that and more than likely it's not playing through to you.
I removed the emojis. Now it was just a single emoji because I think that's what you had originally. Some of the stuff is being worked on. I adjusted the stats part. You had like yours separated with this little thing, so we separated it. Also, when you come into the walls on yours, I've updated this to where now it shows the user profiles at the top.
I have the exact same thing and then I kind of have it in the exact same layout of what you had.
Nate.
All that should be there. As I said, I'm working on the sharing feature now, so that will be coming up. I did remove challenges because I thought we didn't want challenges, but now I see on one of your things there might be challenges, so we can always bring that back. I do actually, I did duplicate this app, so I actually have all of the original with all the features on the side, so we can always...
pull stuff in as we need. But for right now, I just reduced it to just a personal wall and I think just families and then you can create one. This is where I sent in the e-mail this morning.
So if you want to test out creating a new wall and do like the invite, you can do, you know, this is my scroll demo wall. All right, and I'm going to invite.
My wife, so if the person has in this POC, if the person is already registered with their e-mail, if you just use their e-mail, which you can do comma delimited here, it'll do multiple ones, and so we can say create wall. So now I have the scribble demo wall, and so now if we come over, which actually let's just draw on it real quick.
Okay, we want to put down the screen mode devil wall.
Okay, cool. So now that's there. So now if we click on this, we can log out. So now we're going to come over to my wife, so we'll log in. Oh, I must have left on the onboarding. Okay, so she's going to onboard.
Okay, and we'll just put that on our personal for right now. Cool. All right, so now we come into here and so now she has got her invite. So now you'll see these pop up too. So now if you click on this, now we click on it. So now Rob has invited you to the scribble demo wall. I copied your little image here. I thought it was cute. I think we kind of need to add a little more border, but
I think this is cute. Accepted and joins. Now it comes into your next part. So, you know, why did Rob invite you? All right, get started. And then here's the prompt to actually then get started.
And then back to the exact same.
And scribble demo. And then on here you can pick because you had where you could pick multiple options. So I did add that to here.
And let's go. So now, as you can see, now she's got hers. Now I've got mine. She can come in. She can give me a thing if she's right there. And then, as I said, had we had like the play or had they recorded, you would have seen the play option here versus the text.
Yeah.
And that's just a bug. I don't know how it got to that. I think that's just a bug from there.
Would it be helpful?
And then, go ahead.
Oh, go ahead.
I was just to say, and then I removed all the themes except for just because all your stuff was like almost just white. And so I got rid of my scribble theme that I had and just left it white for right now. And then I just added a dark mode one, which was just easy enough. Just so we just do have the option. And then that's pretty much the whole shebang. Minus you can now leave walls as well as
If you're the wall creator, you can even delete the wall too, as well as remove people from it.
So, and all that's baked into, as I said, this, this POC, the POC that I shared.
Awesome.
Would it be helpful to go through the Figma that I created real quick? I think there's a bunch of points you might hit on there, and a few questions we had, and that might just help flavor everything else.
Yap.
Yeah, that would be great.
Because after this, the biggest thing I'll look over is those questions, because it said like...
Yeah, that's like the biggest thing that's got some blockers in it for us.
And then I made that artifact, as I said, for you guys to have, so then kind of encompassed everything. So if we didn't get to some things, everything is there at least too. Oh yeah, I was looking at these today.
I think it's pretty much most of our thoughts and outline questions. The first being, you know, you've got this login screen. The device I'm assuming is going to recognize the user post their first login. I know I saw this is obviously an older one because I pulled it from the Lucid, but you've got that check box for the onboarding and all that. Is someone going to have to go through that every time or is they pull it up and they get...
This first screen on the right-hand side.
So, right, on a mobile app, we don't need to do this. It's just because this is like a web app, I think is the main reason why I had that on there. But yeah, we can get rid of that screen for the mobile app users.
Okay.
Okay, just, you know, you log in once until you log out your, you know, your sync. Okay, perfect. Okay, that was a point of confusion. And then the only other thing with this is this is one of the screens or the set of screens I want, the first one I want Christina to take a look at and handle. I assume that.
Yap, exactly, yes, right, yeah, yeah.
The UI on this is going to be pretty much this, so I'll let her design around it. And I was wondering, is there a plan for an opportunity for any animation here, or should she just create static images?
I mean, if she can create animations, I mean, if you guys want animations, sure, we can put animations in there.
Sorry, I might just be static to start. I'll talk to her about that today.
Okay.
Moving over the canvas, you got the new colors. We're going with those eight.
I'm not sure, you've played the B2B version of the game, correct, in Zoom or Teams?
Yeah, I actually played with the team this morning.
So, we really...
Oh, nice. So we are in love with that canvas and that drawing, the feeling behind it. It almost feels like you're pushing paint around. It's like it's got a very finger paint feeling to it. I'm not sure exactly what it is. It's the size of the brush or, you know, just a few options, but we get a lot of positive feedback on that. So we want to mimic that as close as possible. So that single brush size,
those eight colors, keeping the undo button, which goes back a single step, and then possibly adding an erase button, which we had a lot of requests for where people don't want to undo something, but they want to get rid of a small part of something. And that would also double up as essentially white.
White paint, which people could do over, so if you know they drew, I don't.
Right.
They do something they could write letters over the top in white to kind of like bring out some detail, things like that. And then the other thing you had at one point was the trash button. And I was talking about this a lot earlier.
I think if it had a...
Confirmation.
We would want a trash button for people to start over, start fresh. Let's say they're, you know, through a drawing, like, I don't love this, this isn't what I was thinking. Let me start over. So instead of hitting the undo button 50 times, they can clear the screen or clear, you know, shake the etch sketch. But we would definitely want some sort of pop-up confirmation so that people didn't do it by accident.
Because Abby actually mentioned that a few times using the POC, she cleared her entire drawing out by just clicking the wrong button.
Oh, gotcha, gotcha, okay.
Eric, do we, do we, I mean, do we have enough like user input to even add that feature? I mean, for me, I think that, you know, the one, the one, the one wait line, which is the smallest wait line that Rob currently has, that should be the only, you know, that should be the only selection for drawing.
Undo is great, I mean.
I don't know if we, I would just keep it simple. I mean, I feel like adding an erase button, adding a trash button, I mean, it's just a lot more buttons that.
people will start to strive for perfection.
I mean, we can talk about it internally by reasoning behind it, and so do others.
Yap.
OK, as long as, as long as it's reasoning that has some.
User input. I mean, I just I haven't seen any user input that's, you know, giving us direction as to what people what additional features people want, but if you have that, great.
Yeah, we can talk, what we talk about internally, now's not really the time.
And then the other question I kept getting is about the bounding box in the canvas itself. So we have a very defined one in the B2B game. I think it might just be a function of the background.
Mhm.
And so having a very clear bounding box so people know exactly where they want to draw. Pretty simple.
See if there's anything else random for this, you know, we could we could base it on Christina's work and the background she created, and then color layout, you know, whatever we decide on, just definitely not Roy G. Biv.
And then I also had a little note, if we're going to do the avatar creation screen, it could just be exactly the same.
Hai.
Right, the only difference that I had with that one was I drew like a little circle since it's inside of a circle. So it's just the canvas change, right, yeah, yeah. Right, right, right, okay.
Yap, yeah, so the bounding box would be would be in a circle.
Perfect.
So talking back about the canvas.
So, so I already have the undo button, so I'll just, do you want me to rejigger mine? Because I don't know, have you seen like where the app is currently? Because I made it like your new, yeah, yeah, that's probably the closest, right?
So this was the latest one I saw last night. Yap, and then you added the new colors.
Right.
Right. Okay, so the undo's in the top right, and then we got the brushes in the top left. Do you want to get rid of brushes? Because basically you just said you just want one brush, right?
Yes, we're just going to do one brush.
Okay, so one brush.
In the one that.
The sizing that you just showed us, I think it was maybe second to the right.
was probably best. You might need to finesse it once we start playing with it.
Okay.
No, that's Eric, that's massive. I'm on the app right now, Eric. I mean, you got to get on the app. The one second to the right is a really massive line. The smallest line on Rob's app on my phone is closest to the scribble game today.
So you're talking up here?
Yes, that.
So this is the one, okay, so I'm just basing this off of what I just saw Rob do with the latest version, and this is the one that was selected.
But if you're on the phone and you think it needs to be smaller, then yeah, go for it.
Yeah, and...
I think I think that is either one, either that third one or 4th one to the right is probably close. Yeah, I would say you're right. I would say that third one is probably mimics mostly what we have today. So I would go with that one for the MVP.
Yeah, second from the right.
Right here.
OK, so, and then we'll do the undo button at the top right there. Do you want do you want me to bring that down and have basically all the options at the bottom, or do you want it split? Because it's a...
I think so.
You want all the options at the bottom? Okay.
Yap, I think we, yeah, the prompt should be featured more at the top, uh, just to kind of...
Okay.
keep pushing, you know, because people will question, you know, what was I drawing again? Similar to the current setup, and then anything, colors, undo, and if we go within a race or a trash, we do that as well over to the right hand side.
trash with asking or whatever we're calling it.
Permission, pop-up, yeah, pop-up confirmation. That's what I was looking for.
So, pop-up confirmation or something.
Okay.
Okay, so we'll have the trash, the undo pop-up confirmation, and then do you want me to add white? So technically it'll be 9 colors, so then you can do the kind of make it like the background. So then that third color is always whatever the, or that last color is always whatever the background color is, so you can.
Yeah, I think you know white and race would be interchangeable. Let us, we'd probably just have you add a white option. Let us talk about it a little bit more.
There seems to be some differences of opinion.
Okay.
Okay, I'll put white on there for right now if that's okay.
Okay, cool.
We will play around with it and see if we like it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, cool.
And yeah, and I'll try, because I took screenshots when I was playing the app this morning, so I have the screenshots of the B2B. Oh, that reminds me. We do want the original source code, if you can give us a source code for the B2B.
Yeah, I'll send it over momentarily.
Perfect. Perfect.
Ahh.
home screen. We really like this layout. I think the only question I had was about the logout button.
Most of the time these days, I'm seeing logout buried kind of in your personal options.
And is there ever really a reason for a person to log out? So having it up here by the avatar, we think.
Might confuse or just have people, you know, log out accidentally.
Sorry, I'm just typing, and all this is getting recorded.
I could bounce around some of the apps that I use and I noticed that it was, it's pretty much regulated to the, you know, the profile options section now. And then, you know, we can do, make the avatar maybe even a bit more prominent or have it be a bit more special. And Christina's going to actually work on this screen as well. This will be the second screen that she does backgrounds and whatnot for.
Okay.
OK.
The wall, so actually just showing you showing some of the differences in the wall since the update, where it kind of multiplies a bit, similar to these.
Yap, that's why I modeled it after of your designs as well as this.
Awesome. And I think, you know, I was talking to Abby for a while earlier.
I didn't even finish right here.
So one of the things we talked about was, you know, doing that day's prompt unlocks that section of the wall, lets you see things. And she goes, well, what if your mom missed a day and your nieces didn't?
But she was, she, you know, it was a great prompt, you know, yesterday's was, you know, something, something, something.
your mom would really want to see the girls drugs. So do we unlock everything the next day? Like you can see what people did yesterday.
I guess that's kind of in the same way you would have here.
So there's always like the, we're always pushing people to do today's prompt. You know, you want to see today's stuff, you got to do the prompts and unlock it. Do we unlock everything the next day? Is that a premium feature? Do we let people go back and do previous day's prompts if they have a paid account? I think it's something we'd have to think about once we get into monetization, but I guess just for the short term,
Do we do a reveal after the 24 hours?
So something I had in the prototype was, and when I was thinking about it, because kind of the exact same thing, like, you know, you miss a day for whatever reason, you forgot, like you just wanted to, but you want to go do it. Like I made it to where like you could click on it and then be like, well...
Here's what the prompt would be. Tell me what you would have drawn. And so like it has you then type in like what you would have done and then it saves that and then unlocks the wall. So then you can see everybody else's, but then kind of puts like your comments sort of like you have that, you know, your story of why you missed or whatever. And then you can then see everybody else's.
Like an asterisk, okay.
Yeah, so it's kind of like, you know, tell me why you missed or like why you want to look at this day and then we'll unlock it for you sort of a deal.
So, your story of why you missed?
What do you think, Matthew?
Matt, do you have any thoughts on that?
No, I was playing around with it just now. It was it was it was kind of cool. I think we should think about it a little bit more. I mean...
I think.
We're trying to, we're really trying to impress upon people how important it is to contribute daily and get in that routine and that habit. And if we give people the ability to break it and still get to the reveal, I don't know. I don't love it. You know, if you miss your daily Wordle, can you go back and do it?
The conventional means not.
Right. So I don't know. I'd be happy to, you know, kick around with some ideas and thoughts. Rob, I did like your Goldilocks. I thought it was kind of cool because I think about it in the context of my mom and my kids as well. Like, it's going to be amazing if my mom does this every single day, which I think she will. But if she did miss it for whatever reason, she wasn't feeling well or she had, you know, if she had a doctor's appointment or
It would stink if she couldn't see what my kids did and vice versa.
So I don't know. Maybe we could have a little just kind of internal condo on that, Eric, but.
Definitely open to it. I was talking to Abby a bit about it, and we landed in the same place. All right, so I think the functionality, whatever we might want it to be, is there. We just need to figure out the exact, you know, rule set for it.
Awesome. And then the only other thing was the challenges. So, I mean, I love the challenges. I've been trying to push stuff like that for like 5 years since this was a card game. And we had like a, working with Hasbro, almost like, what's the card in Monopoly where it's like a random event that happens, community chats or whatever it is.
Mmh.
chance cards. So we had those in that version of the game, and this is kind of similar to that. It's like, oh, you can only use your left hand, or you can only do this, you can only use this color. We eventually want to roll that stuff out to kind of bring a lot of life and repeat play into this. I think for the MVP, we want to stick to just injecting a new prompt.
So.
For a family, I mean, so that it can happen in real time even. You know, we're sitting around waiting for dinner, let's do some scribble prompts. So, you know, maybe the mom who started the wall goes to the family game pack and picks a couple to do, or willing to do it at a time. And again, this is a place where that Claude prompt creation could come into play.
where it's eventually starting to learn about the people who are on the wall, what they've drawn in the past, what they're into, what kind of questions they've asked in the past, even like literally what they're doing. I, you know, I made an example of one week it's like, what are you excited for next week in Disney World? And then two weeks later, maybe Claude goes, what was your favorite part of Disney World?
People are like, oh, that's like, how do they know? And you know, that kind of thing. So, but even just to start, lowest level MVP is just a custom user created prompt or one from a similar game pack, like I shared with you yesterday, where everything's kind of divvied up, but we can create one for family, one for coworkers, anything like that, that might not be.
Mm-hmm.
100 in there, but there might be enough to get people going.
Okay, okay. I'll put, I'll put challenges back in place then.
Yeah, and for the time being, we'll just trim it down to prompt injection. And then, you know, once we get this off the ground, then we can start getting, you know, real fun with what we have people do. And because I love some of your ideas. I've got a million from back in the day. I think we could come up with some really cool stuff to get people interested. Even yesterday, my seven-year-old niece called me.
Mm.
And she's all excited because they have a book at her new school that is called Doodle or something similar like that or Doodler or whatever. And it gives you a canvas with a line that's already drawn on it in black. Just a random squiggle or a random whatever. We've actually had this thought before about doing this with the game.
And then she has to draw something over the top of it. And she drew this whole thing about a pirate ship and told a story about a pirate ship. And she was like, so excited. She's going to do one every day. And I'm like, give me 8 weeks and I'll have something else for you to do every day. So
Yeah.
There's a lot of cool stuff we can do.
Awesome.
And sharing super quick, you said you were working on that right now. The more we talk about this with people, the more they realize, hey, this is actually a content creation platform and the ability for people to share this outwardly on their socials or via text or however is super, super important. This is an example of the one that is currently shareable from the B2B game that.
Yap.
pops up on your phone at the end. This is probably the other place or the third place we'd have Christina interject some background art. The prompt being featured is key so that people have context. And then, you know, just say, hey, this person's talking about an adventure they were on. And then they kind of summarize what the drawing means. What's cool about this is now we can add the stories, whether it's.
voice or text. We were playing around a while ago with, and I think you had a question about this and that list of questions we're going to hit.
Currently, the drawings are shared as individual lines, or they're stored as individual lines. So when people have taken a look at it, there's a lot we could do with this when it comes to animation or even like GIFs. So taking like...
Let's say I record a 15-second voice story that goes with this image of me wrestling an alligator. As that's being told, maybe this is being drawn in real time using those strokes, and it's just, you know, elastic banded to the time frame. It's a thought, could be farther off, but that's kind of
One of the things we're thinking about when this comes to Sharan.
Okay.
At the very minimum, a static image, maybe there's room for text or I guess adding voice and sharing that would probably be more complicated because then it would have to be some sort of real or story or have back, I guess would be like background music, but it's technically voiced.
Rob, I'm in a rabbit. I'm in a black hole over here. I just did my first reflection and then it opened up the wall from that day and I got to see Eric's glass of water that he was drinking that day. It's pretty cool. Like the reflection things. It's pretty cool. Yeah.
Yeah.
Sorry to, sorry to, you know, take you guys away from the task at hand.
So yeah.
Source.
No worries.
Any other questions about that or?
Nope, nope. I said I'm trying to get that created right now. Right now it's just spitting out just the image without the border. So I'm trying to get it to actually spit it without the or with the border. So yeah.
And I think all these assets are probably in that code base I'll share with you. I'm not sure, maybe not. I might have them separately.
We'll see what Christina comes back with if I can get you temporary stuff from the B2B game as far as backgrounds and that can help with this.
Okay, perfect.
Yep. And the last thing is the artifact, as always. And it's just kind of trying to determine if and what could be included. Is this...
too big for the scope, is it something that we could do a low level version of? We obviously, we did that work with Mission. And they used Claude to kind of ID all the art, start placing it on a canvas together. It was pretty far from done. You know, it needed a lot of work. One of the things that will expedite that work is we're now getting.
voice and text that actually describe the drawing as opposed to Claude taking not too long, but an amount of time to identify all the drawings. And it did a pretty damn good job, surprisingly, because people were drawing complete nonsense and it got it right a lot of times.
Mm.
So is there like a Goldilocks where it could be, you know, currently it's manual manipulation by the user? So at the end of the game, you've probably seen it, all the drawings show up and you can kind of just push them around. There's some weird movement to it that we need to get rid of. But people do, they make these kind of little murals or drawings and they share that amongst themselves.
Is it possible to, you know, long press a few of the pieces of art, have them pop up similar to stickers, and then you can resize, rotate, and arrange them manually to create something? And is that a precursor to actually having Claude do that?
Um...
So, having Claude do it.
That's not a precursor to it. So those will be two separate things. The clod ways probably for me is easier, but yeah, but the other way.
I, I guess, like a...
I'm leaning more towards the other one first. We could always do the AI Rd. because that's easy enough to add in. But yeah, I want to, I don't know about the clicking all of them and then making it shareable. I'll play with that today. That sounds like honestly a good challenge.
Yeah, and when I say precursor, just an idea only. Obviously, we want this to be something that's automated and then eventually monetized in the future, where you might get X amount of these for based on your subscription level, or you get, you know, you have 5 with the basic subscription. But there are probably people who want to jam on this and create a bunch of them.
Mm.
And that's going to cost us money. And we know that. Every time one of these, you know, mission, I think, gave us, what was it, like 17 to 63 cents, Matt, every time one of these was created. And so we have to take that into consideration because if someone's making 100 of them a week, we'll be in trouble. So is there a token system or something that we can?
you know, start putting forward. And of course, stakeholders love the idea of, hey, you can further monetize this beyond just a small subscription fee.
Mhm, mhm.
Yeah, and you having played the B2B game, Rob, and run sessions, I think.
A lot of feedback that we've gotten from the artifact, and granted those images are moving around and they're a little bit difficult to control, but I think people do get a lot of pleasure and delight in like moving around and trying to create, you know, create a scene, for lack of a better term. So, I mean, once they have it perfect, you know, they save it and they send it out in an e-mail or saying, hey, thanks for joining us today for, you know, today's scribble session.
You know, here's a here's a shared mural of what we've created together, so it's interesting.
Could you share and also save it? Because I mean, some of these, like when you get done, like not only would you want to share, I wouldn't mind saving that to my personal wall and then maybe like adding stuff to it later or something.
For sure. That's really cool.
But yeah, in the same, I mean, this is how I see like stickers on my phone. I'm adding them to an image or messing around where you basically can simply resize or, and we probably want the resize to be, I don't know the name, proportional, like when you hold shift or control.
Mhm.
as opposed to being able to do something like this. Maybe not, I don't know.
You're maintaining the integrity of the original stroke, yeah.
Yes.
I mean, the hard thing is this is on a phone, so I have to like watch that because it's going to be more like pinches and zooms and then, you know, like dragging like that to rotate.
Mhm.
Yeah, I'm trying to remember what app I use it the most in, but it really just when you click on it, it might be Instagram Stories that does it really well. You know, you click on something and it gives you pretty much exactly this. And you can grab, it doesn't have the curved arrow, but you basically grab a corner.
Okay.
And you can spin, or you can grab a corner and you can proportionally.
Go back and forth and then just.
Okay.
Okay, yeah, I'll play with this to see if I can do this. I have a feeling more than likely I can.
I don't know that this, I mean, this will be like in the orange section or, you know, gray possibly later, but yeah, I can at least try and get in the POC.
Yes.
Yeah, we just wanted to get it out there and make sure, because I know we've talked about it a lot. I don't know if we've ever just sat down and talked about it.
Mhm.
I don't know if you've seen the stuff that Mission came back with. Did we ever share that, Matt?
We did.
Okay.
I only got the AI background one.
That's right, yep. And we were still kind of like half and half on that. That's why we were talking about like Christina creating a huge trough of scribbles to help flavor that they would pull and learn from as opposed to being something that's like hyper realistic.
Again, we realized that this could be a ways out, phase two, three, 4, whatever, but we just wanted to put it out there.
Yeah, I want to get that in the POC.
Sorry, my internet bounced real quick.
All right, great. So yeah, so I will take that feedback and I'll start working on this, the app for then tomorrow. I'll also get that meeting fired off. But yeah, so in the meantime, let's look at the board because I said there's some questions on here that are very important, mainly around like the Apple, Apple as well as the AWS.
which I think I shared the Lucid board. You guys should have access to this too, so not only look through here, but yeah, so do you guys have an AWS environment that we can deploy to?
So I had actually asked our AWS guy and he answered me about something completely different. We, I mean, obviously we have an AWS account where we host the B2B game.
Is this something that we would need a new instance for or can this go in the same place? This is something that we do not know. It's not, you know, not something we've dealt with before.
Okay, so you guys have an existing AWS instance. You just need to know whether or not we can host in the exact same instance. Okay, so they do have...
Or is that best practice? Should we start spin up something completely new for this? You know, you tell us.
Okay, I will reach out and let them, because they're more of the experts than I am at this. I think we should be able to use the exact same ones. More likely they'll be partitioned in some way, but they'll still fall in like the exact same accounts, because with AWS you can like create things in different ways. So yeah, so I will work with the team. Who's a good contact for them to reach out to to talk to?
about this.
That would be James or Matt, what's his name? The guy who works with James, that's more on the tech side.
I think it's a James thing. I mean, he's already done. Yeah, but he would he would he would farm it out to Bhasin if he needed that help.
For Bhasin, OK.
Okay, do you have an e-mail so that I can like send an e-mail to him? Or have the team send an e-mail? Okay.
Yap.
Yap, it is.
Let me grab that for you right now.
e-mail is.
Want to put it in the chat, Matt.
Do you want to see? Do you want just James?
I get the scene to it.
You can put a vote on that.
It's just uh...
How do you spell BA?
J.A.
Got it.
**** JA.
All right, those are both in the chat.
Okay, you go.
Yeah, you can ping, if you wanted to ping him directly, he'll get right back to you. I mean, he's super responsive.
I know in the...
When I let Mission in, they gave me a file to deploy within our AWS backend. It was like a...
Is this to?
like a packet or something. I forget exactly what they called it.
And that they'll let them in and do everything that they need to do in there.
Oh, okay. Okay.
Right, we can reach out to them.
All right, the Apple accounts. Do you guys have Apple accounts?
We we don't have anything. Yap.
You have anything with Apple? OK, so no, 'cause in order to even like do the development, like we need Apple IDs, so the devs can even start working in this, so...
Yes, one thing to know.
So since the team, since it's been for them basically three days, they have figured out what their tech stack that they want to use. They are not going to be building each app individually because you can build native versions of the app. They're going to be using React Native and they're going to be using the Expo framework, which is exactly the same framework that I built.
the POC with. So that will offer us both the ability to spin up Android, iOS, as well as the mobile app that you saw. So we will have that. Now having said that, is our goal still to focus on Apple for the going future, or as I said, like...
Mm.
Android, we can do right now without any issues, we can share the, you know, Android stuff, or do we, are we still like heads focused on Apple, because otherwise we're gonna have to like get past this hurdle, because I said we need the dev licenses, we need like the iStore registry, we need all the stuff for this, and you get to start like soon.
We were kind of under the impression it told.
that we would need to focus on, iPhone only, just to make this happen. It sounds like that might not be the case because of the framework you're using.
Right, right. So we will get kind of all of it for one. The thing is, though, on those, you do have to go into each layer and then kind of customize in the area because it makes it as generic as it possibly can. But you still have to go in and like fine tune them as well as like any hardware specific things. So especially like the voice recording.
Mm.
All that would be custom based on the phone, which I know, I think even David said that was even harder on the Android side, but yeah.
Let's, Matt, do you want to just focus on the iOS to start?
I mean, that was the take away I took away from.
Yap.
that initial conversation.
I'm just out, I'm out of my league, so my opinion really doesn't matter.
And this is something, I mean, obviously we revisit this in like phase two or three and we get it Android ready and that's just more sprints in the future.
It.
Yeah, the only challenge with going with BIOS only is that that's going to really influence our beta group of users. I mean, if you have families that are, you know, cross-functional on their phones, they're not going to be a fit for our beta, which that's a huge problem.
Yeah, we know.
So if we can focus on both and that's, you know, it's going to add a little bit of time to the project or not. I say we focus on both because.
I don't know. I mean, I'm a mixed family. I have a wife with an Android. My kids have iPhones. I assume that's not uncommon, but I don't know anything.
What would you recommend, Rob?
Okay.
I mean, we're going to have to start getting, as I said, we'll have to register, get the Apple account now, get the dev licenses to the devs. This would allow us to proceed forward. We'll be using, as I said, that framework that I'm already forgetting the name of. I've already brainfarted it a couple times.
Yeah.
Next one.
But in any case, we'll be able to then target and focus on the iOS side. We'll be able to then do the test flight so that then we can share it. And then we can also spin off copies of Android that then we can be like, these aren't as flushed out. Some features may be ignored, but we have this. We're not going to put a lot of effort into it.
but it'll be available because it'll just be for free.
Okay.
Let's do that.
So, OK.
So for the iOS versions, this is something more that you probably need, Christina, unless you already know. But yeah, we'll have to get like the full list of the models of the iOS phones. Do we want iPad and scope? I know eventually iPad, yes. But I mean, first off, do we want to just start with just the phone?
Yes, just the closest start.
Okay, and as I said, as we get the designs, we'll have to then get the exact like versions to support.
Test management software, so I don't know, do you guys already have like what test management software you're using, like quality assurance software, like what are you using on your current? That was the other reason why we were getting the source code, so if anything we could dig it out of there.
To be honest, we don't know the answer to that question.
I think that would be a white, that would be a white spectrum questionnaire. You might want to just pop that over to Nick.
Okay.
Yeah, if it's, I'll send you that source code right off after we get off the call. If there's nothing in there that you can use, then I can get them on the way.
Mhm.
Okay, perfect.
So, okay, more about the QA, but it said if you don't know that one.
So the AWS environments, again, I don't think you can really answer this. Do we need all three in this phase? So I think they're talking about here, no in this phase. So here they're talking about do we need dev, QA, and prod. So those are just the different.
Environments that you'd stand up inside of your AWS.
And that's so much what we have right now with the P2P. I know there's, yeah, okay.
Yeah, yeah. So, I mean, I think for this initial starting, I think we can just focus on dev.
If that sounds good to you all, because as I said, we won't be able to, you know, we can do the QA in prod as we start to get out into the orange and the gray, which then gets closer to the actual reinvent. By that point, it should be in prod.
Do you want to speak, Dave?
Okay, so here, okay, so yeah, so some of this I think I might have to go play a little more because I'm just recording the final image at the end. I wasn't actually recording all the keystrokes. So I'll have to go take a look at how we're doing that to make sure, because kind of to your point where you want to then take those individual keystrokes and then kind of build an animation of drawing the app.
I need to go revisit that one. But having said that, do you ever envision then allowing them to like click on an image and then edit it later?
I don't know. I don't know what we might do in the future. I know we've talked about people being able to draw on top of others or add to.
Do we allow people to edit ones that were already done?
I'm leaning towards no, but you never know. I think, you know, in that code base, it might, there might be, or I can even ask White Specter, or actually Slalom, who originally did it this way. They had reasoning for.
Yeah.
collecting all those keystrokes. And even when I go into Metabase and I pull up a particular file or a particular drawing, I can pull that code, those keystrokes, and if I throw that into like ChatGPT or whatever, it'll draw the image for me based on that. So I can reproduce the images. There was reasons they did that and.
Mhm.
Everybody that we've, you know, especially the mission kids, when they took a look at that, their eyes lit up. They're like, you can do so much more with this now.
just, you know, and they came from like gaming background, like video gaming backgrounds. Like, there's so much you can do with this if you have that information from every, for every image. Now, so we get into a place where storing that becomes.
Right.
Prohibitive? I'm not sure. I don't know that the number is behind it, but...
I don't think so, because it's really just to the point, as they're saying, it's a vector store. So it's literally just a color and then a start and an end. Slash, if you add like some form of curve, then you obviously add a little bit more detail to that. But yeah.
Yap.
Okay, I don't think that's going to be too bad.
So for now, I just put open, no for now. And then we need to make sure that we're recording the keystrokes. And then maybe down the line, we open this up a little bit more.
account for crash analytics, separate account with either Sentry or Firebase. Okay, so I think they're talking about like the crash analytics. Do you guys have any like mobile crash analytics that you're thinking of? I mean, since you're new to this space, I imagine probably no, and you're probably only in our expertise.
Well, no, yeah, a lot of this is uncharted territory for us.
Yap.
Okay.
K, so...
We are the experts.
Okay, so right now, the POC, the meta app, or inside of Bounteous in our...
GitHub repo, no, Bitbucket. I've spent up the new, I spent up a new Bitbucket repo where now we're going to store then the new mobile app. So now the MVP, the what we're building. Do you guys have right now a location would you want us to store that in or are we okay developing it?
first in-house and then once you guys are ready and want to start taking more of this ownership, we can then transfer the code base over to you.
Is any either of those more problematic or harder than the other? Is there is there a best practice of?
Because I've seen this here, better to decide first. Moving it later requires significant effort.
So this is more around like the pipeline and this is to where like we're using Bitbucket. So when we build out the pipeline, it's in a very specific format. It's developed for Bitbucket. So then when we went to merge this or you know, move this over into your side, then that pipeline would, you know, unless you're using Bitbucket or.
GitHub, you know, basically, as long as, like, if we're using different things, we'll have to readjust it on your side.
Okay, but anybody that we bring on, we can just say, hey, this is coming into the bucket and you need to be familiar with that.
Yeah.
Okay, because I mean, you know, Matt, when we, this is one of the requirements that Marty and Sanju can talk about when we're hiring that in-house person is that this is how it's coming to you. Okay.
Yep. Yeah, it probably makes sense for you guys to own everything now and then it's a handoff at some point.
OK, yeah, I mean, if anything, maybe we can just transition it over there, and then it probably, you know, take a look like maybe a week or two to get the pipeline re-fleshed out on the new on your side.
Yeah, I'm semi-familiar with GitHub. Is Bitbucket comparable? Is it as big? Like, is it used widely?
Yeah, so GitHub and Bitbucket, they both like, they share and steal features, they call them different things. You can pretty much do everything in both. GitHub, you're charged per seat, whereas with Bitbucket, it's like our enterprise inside. And so with the Bitbucket, we can spin up as many as we can as well.
many as we want and add as many people as we want to it. Whereas on GitHub, we have to pay for each individual person. So like we've hit a limit on like adding people. And so that's why I have to use Bitbucket and not GitHub.
OK, and anyone proficient we bring on building itself, OK.
They'll be good in both, yeah.
OK.
And then this last question, do we want to support a web app? So because we're going with the Expo, like what we're doing, sort of like what you saw with my POC, that's using Expo and we're using the web app. So I think when my architect was thinking of this question,
where they were thinking with this one was eventually do you see where you want to merge the B2B and the B2C so that then, like, you could use the web app and then talk to mobile people? Or do you want to keep B2B separate and then have this be like its own D2C and then you have mobile and...
Do you still want to support web apps? So like if somebody wants to launch this as a web app and then talk with mobile people? Because technically you could.
I think they should stay separate, Eric.
Yeah, I agree.
It should say separate and I mean having a web app for this is nice, but if it's going to take time away from the POC, then definitely it can wait.
Okay.
Okay, yeah, and so, yeah, I think we really just need to work on the getting the Apple stuff going. So, yeah, so I'll reach out to you because you guys are going to have to do this on your side and then get the licenses going and then have to, you know, we'll basically be going through you, but working with you on this.
Yap.
Because yeah, we got to get those rolling out now because it said the iOS side we can't do any development on that without these licenses.
How much time and effort does that typically take, Rob? What kind of a lift is that?
I'm going to have to get back to you that because I've never built a mobile app.
Gotcha. Okay.
Yeah, and I'm happy to go through the do the work on it. I'm just pointing me in the right direction. I'll be able to start signing up and getting cards.
So...
Yeah, Eric, that's something you might...
Okay.
Something you might want to just ask James as well. He might be able to support that.
So yeah, I did ask him in that e-mail if this was somehow like wrapped up in our AWS account. Like, do we have anything in, you know, we got it back. So I'll hit him up again.
Yeah, I think him again, please.
Yap.
All right, well, we're a little over and that's everything that I had for today. So yeah, I will get that meeting out for tomorrow so we can go further in the designs and then I will, as I said, work harder on the POC so I have more for the tomorrow. So yeah.
Awesome.
Boss.
Beautiful.
Cool.
Much appreciated, Rob.
All right. Thank you. All right. Have a good day. All right. Bye.
Good stuff. Thank you very much, Rob. Bye, man. Take care.
Talk tomorrow.